Guide to the Stanford University, W. W. Hansen Laboratories of Physics, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- PROPOSALS NOT ACTED UPON, 1964
  - Tentative Proposal to SRI for Subcontract on A Theoretical and Experimental Investigation of Materials Suitable for Multiple Quantum Effects at Millimeter and Submillimeter Wavelengths, by Pantell, (Reference/RFQ No. AMC (E)-28-043-65-00216), September 1964 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Proposal to ONR for A Study of Sequence Order in Proteins, by Pattee, September 1964 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Proposal to Wright-Patterson AFB for Low Loss Microwave Transducers, by Chodorow, October 1964 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- INVESTIGATION OF HIGH POWER PULSED KLYSTRONS
  - Status Reports, March 1,1950 - May 31, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Status Report, ML 117, March 1 - May 31, 1950
    - Status Report, Classified, Jun 1-Sep 30, 1950
    - Status Report, ML 135, Oct 1-Dec 31, 1950
    - Status Report, ML 137, Jan 1-Feb 28, 1951
    - Status Report, ML 145, March 1 - May 31, 1951
    - Status Report, ML 148, Jun 1-Aug 31, 1951
    - Status Report, ML 152, Sep 1-Nov 30, 1951
    - Status Report, ML 159, Dec 1-Feb 29, 1952
    - Status Report, ML 162, March 1 - May 31, 1952
    - Status Report, ML 170, Jun 1-Aug 31, 1952
    - Status Report, ML 187, Sep 1-Nov 31, 1952
    - Status Report, ML 196, Dec 1-Feb 28, 1953
    - Status Report, Classified, March 1 - May 31, 1953
    - Status Report, ML 217, Jun 1-Aug 31, 1953
    - Status Report, ML 226, Sep 1-Nov 31, 1953
    - Status Report, ML 238, Dec 1-Feb 28, 1954
    - Status Report, ML 243, March 1 - May 31, 1954
  - Status Reports, Jun 1, 1954-Mar 31, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Status Report, ML 246, Jun 1-Aug 31, 1954
    - Status Report No.1, ML-ERL, Oct 1-Dec 31, 1954
    - Status Report No.2, ML-ERL, Jan 1-Mar 31, 1955
    - Status Report No.3, ML-ERL, Apr 1-Jun 30, 1955
    - Status Report No.4, ML-ERL, Jul 1-Sep 30, 1955
    - Status Report No.5, ML-ERL, Oct 1-Dec 31, 1955
    - Status Report No.6, ML-ERL, Jan 1-Mar 31, 1956
  - Status Reports, Apr 1, 1956-Jun 30, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Status Report No.7, ML-ERL, Apr 1-Jun 30, 1956
    - Status Report No.8, ML-ERL, Jul 1-Sep 30, 1956
    - Status Report No.9, ML-ERL, Oct 1-Dec 31, 1956
    - Status Report No.10 ML-ERL, Jan 1-Mar 31, 1957
    - Status Report No.11 ML-ERL, Apr 1-Jun 30, 1957
  - Status Reports, Jul 1, 1957-Dec 31, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Status Report No.12 ML-ERL, Jul 1-Sep 31, 1957
    - Status Report No.13 ML-ERL, Oct 1-Dec 31, 1957
    - Status Report No.14 ML-ERL, Jan 1-Mar 31, 1958
    - Status Report No.33 ML 535, Apr 1-Jun 30, 1958
    - Status Report No.34 ML 569, Jul 1-Sep 31, 1958
    - Status Report No.35 ML 585, Oct 1-Dec 31, 1958
- MEDICAL ACCELERATOR PROJECT, Nonr-225(06)
  - Status Reports, Mar 1, 1952-May 31, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - ML 166, March 1 - May 31, 1952
    - ML 167, June 1 - August 31, 1952
    - ML 189, September 1 - November 30, 1952
    - ML 223, June 1 - August 31, 1953
    - ML 224, September 1 - November 30, 1953
    - ML 230, December 1 - February 28, 1954
    - ML 245, March 1 - May 31, 1954
    - ML 247, June 1 - August 31, 1954
    - ML 253, September 1 - November 30, 1954
    - ML 261, December 1 - February 28, 1955
    - ML 268, March 1 - May 31, 1955
    - ML 281, June 1 - August 31, 1955
    - ML 289, September 1 - November 30, 1955
    - ML 299, December 1 - February 29, 1956
    - ML 313, March 1 - May 31, 1956
    - ML 330, June 1 - August 31, 1956
    - ML 355, September 1 - November 30, 1956
    - ML 397, December 1 - February 28, 1957
    - ML 442, March 1 - May 30, 1957
    - ML 460, June 1 - August 31, 1957
    - ML 478, September 1 - November 30, 1957
    - ML 518, March 1, 1952 - May 31, 1958
    - Final Report
- AMERICAN CANCER SOCIETY AND USPHS REPORTS (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, ML 220, September 1, 1952 - August 31, 1953
  - Midyear Report, ML 233, September 1, 1953 - February 28, 1954
  - Annual Report, ML 251, September 1, 1953 - August 31, 1954
  - Midyear Report, ML 260, September 1, 1954 - February 28, 1955
  - Annual Report, ML 285, September 1, 1954 - August 31, 1955
  - Annual Report, ML 351, September 1, 1955 - August 31, 1956
- LINEAR ELECTRON ACCELERATOR STUDIES A.E.C. Contract AT (04-3)-21 (Project Agreement Nos. 1 and 2)
  - Reports, 1953-1955 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Status Report, July 1 - September 30, 1953, ML 222
    - Status Report, October 1 - Decem. 31, 1953, ML 228
    - Status Report, January 1 - March 31, 1954, ML 237
    - Status Report, April 1 - June 30, 1954, ML 244
    - Status Report, July 1 - September 30, 1954, ML 248
    - Status Report, October 1 - Decem. 31, 1954, ML 257
    - Status Report, January 1 - March 31, 1955, ML 267
    - Status Report, April 1 - June 30, 1955, ML 272
    - Technical Report, December 1954, ML 252
    - Technical Report, October 1955, ML 282
    - Status Report, July 1 - September 30, 1955, ML 286
  - Reports, 1955-1957 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Status Report, October 1 - Dec. 31, 1955, ML 292
    - Technical Report, December 1955, ML 288
    - Technical Report, April 1956, ML 303
    - Status Report, January 1 - March 31, 1956, ML 305
    - Extension of Project Agreement No. 2, May 1956
    - Status Report, April 1 - June 30, 1956, ML 320
    - Status Report, July 1 - September 30, 1956, ML 347
    - Status Report, October 1 - Decem. 31, 1956, ML 367
    - Technical Report, March 1957, ML 379
    - Status Report, January 1 - March 31, 1957, ML 416
  - Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Status Report, April 1 - June 30, 1957, ML 432
    - Status Report, July 1 - September 30, 1957, ML 448
    - Status Report, October 1 - Decem. 31, 1957, ML 485
    - Status Report, January 1 - March 31, 1958, ML 504
    - Technical Report, March 1958, ML 491
    - Status Report, April 1 - June 30, 1958, ML 520
    - Technical Report, A Theoretical Analysis of Linear Accelerators Using Equivalent Circuits and Cavity Normal Modes, by K. Dedrick ML 439
  - Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Technical Report, Theory of the Constant Gradient Linear Electron Accelerator, by R. B. Neal ML 513
    - Status Report, July 1 - September 30, 1958, ML 557
    - Status Report, October 1 - Decem. 31, 1958, ML 581
    - Status Report, January 1 - March 31, 1959, ML 612
    - Status Report, April 1 - June 30, 1959, ML 640
    - Status Report, July 1 - December 31, 1959, ML 687
  - Miscellaneous Technical Reports, 1953-1958 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - ML 212, Design and Performance of a High Power Pulsed Klystron, September 1953
    - ML 274, Choice of a Wavelength and Characteristic Parameters in the Design of the Linear Elelctron Accelerator, September 1955
    - ML 331, The Travelling-Wave Frequency Multiplier, July 1957
    - ML 383, Free Radicals in Biological Systems, undated
    - ML 401, Development in Beam-Type Maser Amplifiers and Oscillators, June 1957
    - ML 402, Final Reports of Stanford-Litton L-Band Klystron Project, June 1957
    - ML 403, Measurements of Interaction Impedance, June 1957
    - ML 404, An Exponential Beam Condenser, June 1957
    - ML 406, Deflection Focusing, June 1957
    - ML 435, Antioxidant Determinations by the Use of a Stable Free Radical, April 1958
    - ML 469, Analysis of the Fast-Wave Traveling-Wave Tube, December 1957
    - ML 471, Variational Principle for Small-Amplitude Disturbances of Electron Beams, January 1958
  - Miscellaneous Technical Reports, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - ML 473, An Analysis of the Large Signal Behaviour of Klystrons by the Method of Non-Linear Oscillation Theory, January 1958
    - ML 480, same as ML 471
    - ML 488, A Perpetual Analysis of the Equations for Electrostatic Space-Charge Flow and its Application to the Production of Hollow Beams from a Torodial Cathode, undated
    - ML 492, The Kinematics of Growing Waves, April, 1958
    - ML 499, Large Signal Klystron Theory; A Steady State Self-Consistant Space-Charge Flow, April, 1958
    - ML 506, Amplifying and Evanescent Waves: Convective and Non-Convective Instability, 1958
  - Miscellaneous Technical Reports, 1958-1960 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - ML 505, same as ML 471
    - ML 511, Solution to the Equations of Space-Charge Flow by the Method of the Separation of Variables, undated
    - ML 521, General Power Relationships for Positive and Negative Nonlinear Resistive Elements, undated
    - ML 527, Notes on Trajectory-Modulated Microwave Devices, June 1958
    - ML 529, The Coupling of Modes and Variational Analysis of the Resonant Slot Coupled Periodic Cavity Chain, July 1958
    - ML 590, Final Report on Microwave Tube Research, March, 1959
    - ML 740, Non-Synchronous Beam Loading in Linear Electron Accelerators, August 1960
  - Miscellaneous Reports (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Reports (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Wollaston Wire Wattmeter and Impedence Measuring Device, by Carson, January 1942 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Klystron Synchronizer, by Learned, January 1942 (Box 36, Folder 5)